[
  {
    "id": "755",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a subnet in your VPC you lose how many ip addresses to AWS reserve allocation?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["5"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "756",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a subnet in your VPC which address do you lose to AWS reservation for broadcast (even though AWS doesn't support broadcast)?",
      "answers": [
        "the last address",
        "the first address",
        "the second address",
        "the third address",
        "the fourth address"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the last address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "757",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a subnet in your VPC which address do you lose to AWS reservation for the network address?",
      "answers": [
        "the last address",
        "the first address",
        "the second address",
        "the third address",
        "the fourth address"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the first address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "758",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a subnet in your VPC which address do you lose to AWS reservation for the VPC router?",
      "answers": [
        "the last address",
        "the first address",
        "the second address",
        "the third address",
        "the fourth address"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the second address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "759",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a subnet in your VPC which address do you lose to AWS reservation for the DNS server?",
      "answers": [
        "the last address",
        "the first address",
        "the second address",
        "the third address",
        "the fourth address"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the third address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "760",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a subnet in your VPC which address do you lose to AWS reservation for future use?",
      "answers": [
        "the last address",
        "the first address",
        "the second address",
        "the third address",
        "the fourth address"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the fourth address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "761",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of gateway do you use to allow private EC2 instances to access 0.0.0.0/0?",
      "answers": [
        "NAT Gateway",
        "Internet Gateway",
        "Public Gateway",
        "Private Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NAT Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "762",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In which subnet do you place your NAT Gateway?",
      "answers": [
        "Public subnet",
        "Private subnet"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Public subnet"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "763",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What do you need to create for your NAT Gateway in order for it to be reachable?",
      "answers": [
        "an Elastic ip Address",
        "a DNS Name"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["an Elastic ip Address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "764",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of route do you need to create in your VPC public route table in order for your NAT Gateway to be reachable?",
      "answers": [
        "a route to 0.0.0.0/0 with a target of the NAT Gateway",
        "a route to 0.0.0.0/0 with a target of the Internet Gateway",
        "a route to 0.0.0.0/0 with a target of the NAT Instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a route to 0.0.0.0/0 with a target of the NAT Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "765",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How do you ensure your NAT Gateway can be fault tolerant?",
      "answers": [
        "create a NAT Gateway in each of your AZs",
        "create a NAT Gateway in another region",
        "create a NAT Instance in each of your AZs",
        "create a NAT Instance in another region"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["create a NAT Gateway in each of your AZs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "766",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NAT Gateways fail-over _________ if you have them configured with one in each of your AZs?",
      "answers": [
        "automatically",
        "using ENS",
        "using EQS",
        "using CloudWatch Events"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["automatically"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "767",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NAT Gateways are in a Security Group?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "768",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With a NAT Instance you need to disable the ________ on the instance?",
      "answers": [
        "Source/Destination check",
        "Inbound/Outbound check",
        "Public/Private check"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Source/Destination check"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "769",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NAT Instances are behind a ________?",
      "answers": [
        "Security Group",
        "NACL",
        "NAT Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Security Group"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "770",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NAT Instances must be in a ________?",
      "answers": [
        "public subnet",
        "private subnet",
        "Security Group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["public subnet"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "771",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NAT Gateways scale automatically up to _____?",
      "answers": [
        "10Gbps",
        "10Mbps",
        "5Gbps"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["10Gbps"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "772",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Do you need to patch NAT Gateways?",
      "answers": [
        "yes",
        "no",
        "sometimes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["no"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "773",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Are NAT Gateways associated with a Security Group?",
      "answers": [
        "yes",
        "no",
        "sometimes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["no"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "774",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NAT Gateways are automatically assigned _______?",
      "answers": [
        "a public ip address",
        "a private ip address",
        "a security group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a public ip address"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "775",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You need to update your public route tables to point ________ to your NAT Gateways?",
      "answers": [
        "0.0.0.0/0",
        "your Security Groups",
        "your EC2 instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["0.0.0.0/0"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "776",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which are more secure, NAT Gateways or NAT Instances?",
      "answers": [
        "NAT Gateways",
        "NAT Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NAT Gateways"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "777",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can associate a subnet to how many NACLs?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "many"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["1"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "778",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can associate a NACL to how many subnets?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "many"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["many"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "779",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can deploy a NACL to how many VPCs?",
      "answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "many"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["1"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "780",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACLs can be associated with many VPCs?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "781",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you create a new public NACL, all inbound and outbound routes is ________ by default?",
      "answers": [
        "allowed",
        "denied"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["denied"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "782",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Using NACL inbound rules you can deny __________?",
      "answers": [
        "a specific ip address",
        "an ip address range",
        "a specific DNS name",
        "a top level DNS name"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a specific ip address",
        "an ip address range"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "783",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACL rules are evaluated in _________?",
      "answers": [
        "numeric order",
        "alphabetic order",
        "in order by creation time"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["numeric order"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "784",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When NACL rules are evaluated, a rule in the order first takes precidence over following rules?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "785",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACL rule changes take effect _________?",
      "answers": [
        "eventually",
        "immediately",
        "at intervals configured through the console"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["immediately"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "786",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which are assessed first, NACLs or Security Groups?",
      "answers": [
        "NACLs",
        "Security Groups",
        "neither"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NACLs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "787",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The default VPC automatically has a default ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "NACL",
        "Network Instance"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NACL"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "788",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The default VPC default NACL which _________?",
      "answers": [
        "allows all inbound and outbound traffic",
        "denies all inbound and outbound traffic",
        "allows all inbound traffic",
        "allows all outbound traffic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["allows all inbound and outbound traffic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "789",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "All new custom NACLs _________ by default?",
      "answers": [
        "allow all inbound and outbound traffic",
        "deny all inbound and outbound traffic",
        "deny all inbound traffic",
        "allow all outbound traffic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["deny all inbound and outbound traffic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "790",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "To allow traffic to new custom NACLs you _________?",
      "answers": [
        "add rules",
        "add ports",
        "add port ranges",
        "add subnets"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["add rules"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "791",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Each ______ in your VPC must be associated with a NACL?",
      "answers": [
        "subnet",
        "EC2 instance",
        "Security Group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["subnet"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "792",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you don't explicitly associate a with a NACL, it will automatically be ________?",
      "answers": [
        "associated with the default NACL",
        "associated with the default Security Group",
        "associated with the default Network Instance",
        "denied all inbound and outbound routes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["associated with the default NACL"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "793",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you associate a NACL with a subnet, the previous subnet-NACL relationship is _______?",
      "answers": [
        "removed",
        "subordinated",
        "promoted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["removed"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "794",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACLs can't span AZs?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "795",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACLs contain a numbered list of rules that is evaluated _______, starting with ________?",
      "answers": [
        "in ascending order, the lowest numbered rule",
        "in descending order, the highest numbered rule",
        "randomly, a randomly selected rule"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["in ascending order, the lowest numbered rule"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "796",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACLs have separate inbound and outbound rules, where each rule ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "either allows or denies traffic",
        "allows traffic",
        "denies traffic"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["either allows or denies traffic"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "797",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "NACLs are ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "stateful",
        "stateless"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["stateless"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "798",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You should allow ephemeral ports on the _______ rules only?",
      "answers": [
        "outbound",
        "inbound"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["outbound"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "799",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Ephemeral ports are used to ______ the outbound port?",
      "answers": [
        "randomize",
        "block",
        "allow"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["randomize"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "800",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An Application ELB must be associated with ______?",
      "answers": [
        "at least 2 subnets",
        "a subnet",
        "a Security Group",
        "at least 2 Security Groups"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["at least 2 subnets"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "801",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With a VPC using an Application ELB, each subnet connected to the Application ELB must be ______?",
      "answers": [
        "public facing",
        "internal facing",
        "in a NACL (i.e. be public facing)",
        "in a Network Instance  (i.e. be public facing)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["public facing"]
    }
  }
]
